She's losing control again.
Boarding Gate is a thriller, drama film directed by Olivier Assayas.
A beautiful woman, Sandra, seduces a wealthy businessman, Miles Rennburg.
Little does he realise that she has been sent to kill him at the
behest of her boyfriend/crime partner, Lester.
Controlling all this is Sue, Lester's wife.
Sandra, played by Asia Argento.
Miles Rennberg, played by Michael Madsen.
Sue Wang, played by Kelly Lin Hsi-Lei.
Kay, played by Kim Gordon.
Lester Wang, played by Carl Ng Ka-Lung.
Andrew, played by Alex Descas.
Boarding Gate is a 2007 French thriller film about the sophisticated power plays between a debt-ridden underworld
entrepreneur, his provocative and ambitious ex-associate and a manipulative young couple who employ her.
Written and directed by Olivier Assayas, the film features an international cast
comprising Asia Argento, Michael Madsen, Carl Ng and Kelly Lin.
Kim Gordon also plays a supporting role as an enigmatic businesswoman
forced to intervene as events unfold in Hong Kong.
The film premiered 18 May at the 2007 Cannes Film Festival
and later opened in France on 22 August 2007.
The film explores themes of paris, france, chase, stalker, murder, hong kong.
The tone is emotional and intense.